<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rdf:RDF
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">

<channel rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/">
    <title>PHP-GTK</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>The PHP-GTK extension Web site</description>
    <items>
        <rdf:Seq>
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2009-05-28" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2008-02-29" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2007-06-17" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-07-17" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-07-15" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-01-18" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2004-12-20" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2004-11-12" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/download.php" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/docs-rss.php" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-dev&amp;m=109104992017688&amp;w=2" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/news.rss" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/wiki/" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/docs.php" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://developers.slashdot.org/developers/04/07/21/2328224.shtml" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-general&amp;m=109029957326705&amp;w=2" />
        </rdf:Seq>
    </items>
</channel>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2009-05-28">
 <title>We're still here!</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
Rumours of PHP-GTK's death have been greatly exaggerated! The project is
very much still alive, but we're waiting for PHP 5.3 to come out, and also some
work needs to be done on the Cairo extension before a new release can be made.
This should be completed soon. This release will come with support for GTK 2.14
and 2.16, Cairo, and PHP 5.3.

The next release will also include official installers for Windows and Mac OSX,
and an installer script (thank you bob) for Linux.

If you are interested in helping out with the project, there are many ways to
get involved. Contributions of code and tests are always welcome. You can get
in touch on the php.gtk.dev mailing list.  We're also looking at improving the
PHP-GTK documentation and website, for which we have the php.gtk.doc mailing
list. Alternatively, join us in #php-gtk on the Freenode IRC network.</p>
 </description>
 <dc:date>2009-05-28</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2007-06-17">
 <title>PHP-GTK 2 is Here!</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
After a long development and QA cycle, we are proud to release version 2.0 of PHP-GTK.
This release marks PHP-GTK 2 as stable and comes with support for GTK+ versions 2.6
through 2.12. Although support for more recent versions than 2.8 is not 100% complete, we
hope to cover as much of the API as possible in upcoming releases.

This release comes with support for custom GTypes and signals, more API coverage, and the
usual slew of bug fixes. Take a look at the Changelog for detailed information on changes
since the beta.

If you're looking to learn PHP-GTK, the documentation is a great place to start. There's
also an excellent book from Apress by Scott Mattocks on the topic. We hope you will enjoy
developing applications with PHP-GTK 2. Please don't hesitate to file bug reports at the
bug tracker, or give us feedback on the php-gtk-general mailing list. Have fun! 
 </description>
 <dc:date>2008-02-29</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2007-06-17">
 <title>PHP-GTK 2 Beta!</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
The PHP-GTK team is proud to announce the release of a beta version of
PHP-GTK 2. This release, aptly named "extension extravaganza", brings
with it tons of new features that you can look forward to:
 - Overall API coverage is now at 90%, with over 95% coverage for just
the Gtk+ API.
 - The GtkTreeView widget has been significantly enhanced with custom
model and drag-and-drop support.
 - Basic clipboard functionality is now supported.
 - Exciting new cross-platform widgets now available through the GtkSpell,
GtkExtra, GtkHTML3, libsexy and Scintilla extensions.
 - Gtk+ versions 2.8 and 2.10 are now supported, which brings along a host
of new features such as enhanced printing support; revamped GtkIconView,
GtkNotebook; GtkPlug/Socket support for Win32; and a variety of new widgets
like GtkStatusIcon and GtkAssistant.
 - The usual set of bug fixes and unit test additions.

Head over to the download section and grab a tarball. PHP-GTK 2 is now one
step closer to a final release. Thanks to entire PHP-GTK team for making
this release possible!
 </description>
 <dc:date>2007-06-17</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2007-01-12">
 <title>PHP-GTK Teams for the PHPThrowdown</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
The PHPThrowdown is a competition to see which team or individual can build the best
application in 24 hours. Its a test of skill and stamina. Most people expect to see
a whole bunch of web applications, but we here in the PHP-GTK community know that the
best applications are written with PHP-GTK. To help prove this point to the rest of the
world, a few teams are being organized to enter PHP-GTK applications into the contest.
If you are interested in joining (or leading) a team, be sure to sign up on the PHP-GTK
PHPThrowdown Team organization form.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2007-01-12</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-12-13">
 <title>December News</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
Interest in PHP-GTK is growing, and this is evident by the increasing
number of hits at the community site. The site provides useful tips
and code samples for PHP-GTK, be sure to stop by. Also, Christian
created a map which tells you where PHP-GTK 2 developers and users
are located. Join us on #php-gtk on Freenode and add yourself!

KateOS, a multitasking operating system; includes a package manager written 
entirely in PHP-GTK 2! This is the first time any distribution has adopted
PHP-GTK 2 at such a level; we hope this trend continues!

The Chinese translation of the PHP-GTK 2 manual has now begun. If you
are interested in contributing to the documentation or development of
PHP-GTK 2 then get in touch with us, and help in making a faster release!

Callicore is a framework for PHP-GTK 2 and provides a set of
re-usable classes designed to make application development quicker and
painless. Though no releases have been made yet, the code from the
repository is pretty usable.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-12-13</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-09-22">
 <title>Taking Conferences by Storm</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
It's conference season in the PHP world and no PHP conference would be complete
without a PHP-GTK 2 presentation (you hear that DCPHP!). Earlier this month
Andrei, demonstrated how easy it is to create powerful desktop applications
with PHP-GTK 2 at PHP|Works in Toronot. Next, in October, Scott will be
speaking at the Zend/PHP Conference. Finally, in early November, Steph will
talk about the new features of PHP-GTK 2 at the International PHP Conference 
and demonstrate how to make lightweight cross-platform applications.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-08-10</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-09-22">
 <title>Online Help</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
While the development team works hard to finish the API (90% coverage is not
far off), a new set of online tutorials has sprung up recently kksou.com. The 
tutorials are short and to the point. They cover those nagging issues that 
don't necessarily prevent you from completing your application, but add a great
deal to the finished product.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-08-10</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-08-10">
 <title>Documentation Filling Out</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
This week, the PHP-GTK 2 documentation broke the 44.44% barrier: nearly
half of the classes and their methods, properties and signals are
documented. PHP-GTK 2 consists of 202 classes with nearly 2,900 methods,
and many signals and properties. As the documentation matures, PHP-GTK 2
becomes easier to work with as the answers to many common problems become
easier to find.

We ask you to help us fill in the white spaces and create examples for
others to learn from. Writing documentation not only helps the project, 
but also helps you learn through experimenting with new methods, and gain
a better understanding of the inner workings of the project. Interested? 
The doccing tutorial explains the first steps, and the php-gtk-doc mailing
list is the central place for all manual issues. All help creating examples
and writing or translating documentation, is appreciated.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-08-10</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-07-17">
 <title>PHP-GTK 2 Alpha Re-release</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
Apparently, PEAR infrastructure tools (due to a deficiency in PHP's
version_compare() function) cannot handle a version modifier called "zeta". We
had to rename it to good old "alpha", re-package and re-release. Download it if you plan
to use PEAR's or gnope.org's packages.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-07-17</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-07-15">
 <title>PHP-GTK 2 Zeta Release</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
  After a long development cycle, PHP-GTK team is proud to announce the first
  official preview release of PHP-GTK 2. Since everyone has been
  patiently waiting for this release for quite a while, we have
  decided to skip a few letters of the Greek alphabet and go straight to
  zeta, which does not get nearly enough respect in the software world compared
   to its brethren. So, without further ado, please welcome PHP-GTK 2.0.0 Zeta!
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-07-15</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-05-18">
 <title>PHP-GTK 2 Resources</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
The number of PHP-GTK 2 resources has been climbing steadily as development
continues. As it stands now there are eight PHP-GTK 2 packages available from
PEAR. The availability of the PHP-GTK 2 documentation provides an online
resources for developers needing help with the PHP-GTK 2 API. Included in the
online documentation is a new tutorial on using Glade with PHP-GTK 2. In
addition several websites devoted to PHP-GTK 2 have cropped up providing a wide
range of resources. Finally, the first PHP-GTK 2 book, Pro PHP-GTK, has been 
published. All of these resources should provide a strong launching point for 
any developer wanting to get a head start working with the soon-to-be-released 
alpha version of PHP-GTK 2.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-05-18</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-02-28">
 <title>Moving toward a release of PHP-GTK 2</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
This month PHP-GTK 2 has continued its march toward an initial release. Andrei
has been working through bug fixes and implementing new features. Recently he 
added the ability to use GtkListStores and GtkTreeStores as if they were 
iterators or arrays. This makes it much easier to work with data models for 
GtkTreeView and GtkComboBox. The documentation team has been working hard to 
fill out the docs. Several new pages have been added and the PHP-GTK 2 docs 
will soon make their first appearance on the PHP-GTK website.

Even though PHP-GTK 2 is not quite stable yet, several applications have been 
developed using the CVS version. There are now four PHP-GTK 2 packages 
available on PEAR including the newly added Gtk2_ScrollingLabel and 
Gtk2_PHPConfig. Christian Weiske has released the first game developed with 
PHP-GTK 2: Minesweeper. 
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-02-28</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2006-01-23">
 <title>PHP-GTK 2 Progress</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
Development of PHP-GTK 2 is steadily picking up pace. The last month has seen
plenty of activity not only in commits to CVS but in other parts of the PHP-GTK
2 community also:
 - The PHP-GTK 2 documentation is filling out. More classes have been
   documented and given examples (especially the GtkTree* classes).
 - Source code highlighting has been added to the PHP-GTK 2 manual.
 - Most of the get_size* methods have been implemented.
 - 85% of all methods and properties have been implemented. The other 15% need
   to be written by hand, and more are being added every week. (Some
   automatically generated methods may not be implemented correctly and will
   have to be re-written by hand. Therefore, the actual coverage figures may be
   slightly lower than those above)
 - The Gnope installer has been downloaded over 8000 times since its release
   last month.
 - Gtk2_PHPConfig an application that makes it easy to modify php.ini files,
   has been proposed on PEAR by Anant Narayanan.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2006-01-23</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-12-11">
 <title>Gnope 1.0 Released</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
  Version 1.0 of the Gnope Installer has
  been released. The Gnope installer helps to set up a full featured PHP-GTK2
  installation on a Windows system with just a few clicks. It is designed to
  make installation of PHP-GTK2 and PHP-GTK2 applications quick and easy. For
  more information or to download Gnope visit 
  http://www.gnope.org.
 </description>
 <dc:date>2005-12-11</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-10-19">
 <title>October News</title>
 <link>http://gtk.php.net</link>
 <description>
  Christian Weiske has written an article for PHP Magazin titled "Rapit
  Application Development Mit PHP-GTK" which discusses creating
  applications using PHP-GTK and Glade.

  An unofficial version of PHP-GTK 2 for Windows can be found at
  http://ftp.emini.dk/pub/php/win32/gtk2/ If you are interested in helping test
  PHP-GTK 2 on Windows, please send your comments to the dev mailing list
 </description>
 <dc:date>2005-10-21</dc:date>
</item>
 
<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-04-22">
    <title>PHP-GTK 2 at the International PHP Conference</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>
     Jeremy Johnstone will be presenting a talk titled "GUI Development in
     PHP-GTK2" at the International PHP Conference in November. Anyone going
     to the conference should be sure to check out his talk. The discussion
     includes "in depth coverage of developing a GUI application in PHP-GTK2
     including tools you can use to allow you to rapidly develop new applications." 
    </description>
    <dc:date>2005-07-25</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-04-22">
    <title>Win9x Support in PHP 5.1</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>
     There is talk on the PHP Internals mailing list about removing support for
     Win9x (95/98/2000/ME) from PHP 5.1. For most PHP developers this isn't much
     of a big deal but for PHP-GTK 2 developers it may have a much more significant
     impact. If you have reasons to keep Win9x support in PHP 5, make sure to voice
     your opinion!
    </description>
    <dc:date>2005-07-25</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-04-22">
    <title>PHP-GTK 1.0.2 Released</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>
     PHP-GTK 1.0.2 is a minor release that fixes a bug in the build process
     that prevented PHP-GTK from being installed with the newly released PHP
     4.4.x branch.
    </description>
    <dc:date>2005-07-15</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-04-22">
    <title>Getting Ready for PHP-GTK 2</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>
     PHP-GTK 2 is getting closer and closer to a first release every day.
     At the International PHP Conference, Andrei gave a talk about the 
     current status of PHP-GTK 2 and the direction it is heading. Since then,
     excellent progress has been made with trees and editable cells. Parameter
     reflection has also been added thanks to Christian. The lastest efforts
     have led to the first set of practical applications written with PHP-GTK
     2. Christian's reflection browser makes it easy to take a look at the
     inner workings of PHP-GTK 2 classes and can be used as simple documentation.
    </description>
    <dc:date>2005-05-18</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-04-22">
    <title>A Message From Andrei</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>I finished porting the first demo from PyGTK, the stock
    item browser. It's in demos/stock-browser.php and in the process I've
    implemented a fair amount of new GtkTreeView/GtkListStore functions.
    PHP-GTK 2 is coming along!
    Maybe a very early alpha release is due...
    -Andrei
    Any tester or developers interested in helping (Especially to port old
    override files so that CList and CTree work) please contact the PHP-GTK
    Dev mailing list.
    In other news, Christian Weiske is making steady progress on the
    documentation system. Docs skeletons can now be automatically generated
    for all of the classes that have been implemented so far. Read his post
    to the documentation mailing list for more details.</description>
    <dc:date>2005-04-22</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2005-03-21">
    <title>PHP-GTK 2 Making Progress</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>PHP-GTK 2 is making great strides toward a working release.
    Andrei's relentless work has lead to a current CVS version that can run
    non-trivial scripts. See the general mailing list archives for an example.
    Take a look at the change log for the latest updates.</description>
    <dc:date>2005-03-22</dc:date>
</item>

</rdf:RDF>
