<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rdf:RDF
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">

<channel rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/">
    <title>PHP-GTK</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>The PHP-GTK extension Web site</description>
    <items>
        <rdf:Seq>
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2004-11-12" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/download.php" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/docs-rss.php" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-dev&amp;m=109104992017688&amp;w=2" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/news.rss" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/wiki/" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://gtk.php.net/docs.php" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://developers.slashdot.org/developers/04/07/21/2328224.shtml" />
            <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-general&amp;m=109029957326705&amp;w=2" />
        </rdf:Seq>
    </items>
</channel>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/about/news-2004-11-12">
    <title>Small steps into a better world</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>While work continues on PHP-GTK 2, there has been some big news with PHP-GTK 1. The continuing documentation efforts have produced two new tutorials and lots of new doc pages. To go along with all of the new documentation, Christian Weiske has released manualBrowser, a PHP-GTK application to make it easier to read and search the docs offline. The folks over at PEAR have even jumped on the PHP-GTK bandwagon. There are two new gtk classes and a new PHP-GTK interface for PHPUnit.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-11-12</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/download.php">
    <title>PHP-GTK 1.0.1 released</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/download.php</link>
    <description>PHP-GTK version 1.0.1 is the first release in nine months. However, this release is also proof that activity in the PHP-GTK camp has indeed increased and is rapidly moving along toward a stable PHP-GTK 2. PHP-GTK 1.0.1, affectionately termed the "you thought we were done?" version, implemented and exposed some new methods for GtkToolbar, reimplemented Gdk::cursor_new_from_pixmap() "so it actually works," and updated the build system. See the changelog for full details. In other news, the manual has been updated to include syntax highlighting (coloring) in the code examples.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-08-09</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/docs-rss.php">
    <title>Documentation updates listed on PHP-GTK Web site</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/docs-rss.php</link>
    <description>The PHP-GTK Web site now features a regularly updated listing of documentation updates. The listing is displayed on the home page and is updated every night when the manual is updated from CVS. The updates are listed in reverse chronological order (the newest at the top), and the latest fifteen updates are shown at any given time. In addition, a documentation update feed is available in RSS format.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-08-05</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-dev&amp;m=109104992017688&amp;w=2">
    <title>PHP-GTK 2 is go for GTK+ 2.4</title>
    <link>http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-dev&amp;m=109104992017688&amp;w=2</link>
    <description>In a thread on php-gtk-dev entitled "Gtk+ 2.2 or 2.4?", developers discussed whether to base PHP-GTK 2 on GTK+ 2.2 or 2.4. The decision was quickly made, with no opposition or argument, to proceed with using GTK+ 2.4. For more information on GTK+ 2.4, read this post and this post.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-07-29</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/news.rss">
    <title>PHP-GTK RSS feed added</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/news.rss</link>
    <description>The addition of an RSS feed allows the PHP-GTK Web site to disseminate its news content throughout many different channels. Other sites may now use the feed to aggregate news content from this site.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-07-28</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/">
    <title>Manual search bug fixed</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/</link>
    <description>A bug has been fixed in the search functionality of the PHP-GTK Web site that caused problems when searching on the manual. Now, searches on connect, window, child, beep, etc. return actual results instead of "cannot be found" messages. Other upgrades to the manual search functionality are likely to follow.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-07-28</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/wiki/">
    <title>New PHP-GTK wiki</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/wiki/</link>
    <description>We have set up a new wiki that is faster and more easily manageable than our previous wiki. In addition, the new wiki is now internally a part of the PHP-GTK Web site. Special thanks go to Manuel Kiessling who contributed server resources to host the PHP-GTK Wiki up until the present. In other news, International PHP Magazine's PHP Barnstormer made special mention of the increased activity here at PHP-GTK in this week's issue.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-07-27</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://gtk.php.net/docs.php">
    <title>Documentation updates</title>
    <link>http://gtk.php.net/docs.php</link>
    <description>Thanks to Christian Weiske, GtkCTree and GtkCList have both received some much-needed documentation. Andrei Zmievski has also implemented a nightly build system so the documentation can be updated regularly on the site as content is added/updated by our documentation team. Also, notice that a "whole site" search selection has been added to the search drop-down box. This feature uses Google to search the PHP-GTK Web site.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-07-22</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://developers.slashdot.org/developers/04/07/21/2328224.shtml">
    <title>Slashdot mention</title>
    <link>http://developers.slashdot.org/developers/04/07/21/2328224.shtml</link>
    <description>The increase in PHP-GTK community activity and interest in PHP-GTK 2 has afforded this site a mention on Slashdot. Thanks to Joel De Gan for posting to Slashdot.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-07-22</dc:date>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-general&amp;m=109029957326705&amp;w=2">
    <title>PHP 5 release sparks renewed interest in PHP-GTK</title>
    <link>http://marc.theaimsgroup.com/?l=php-gtk-general&amp;m=109029957326705&amp;w=2</link>
    <description>Since the release of PHP 5.0.0 last week, the PHP-GTK mailing lists have seen a sharp spike in activity due mostly to interest in PHP-GTK 2.0, the release of which is still in the future. This activity has brought about a massive call for updates to the current PHP-GTK documentation and Web site, with the effort geared toward promoting the extension and making the site and documentation more thorough and user friendly. This progress is now underway. Already, much-needed updates are being made to the documentation, and the Web site is undergoing new development to provide better resources to visitors. For more information regarding the recent developments in the PHP-GTK community and the status of PHP-GTK, please read Andrei Zmievski's "Letter to the Community" post and join the php-gtk-general mailing list to follow along with the activity. The forthcoming PHP-GTK version 2.0 will bind GTK+ 2 to PHP 5. Until then, PHP-GTK 1.0.0 works only with PHP 4.</description>
    <dc:date>2004-07-20</dc:date>
</item>

</rdf:RDF>
